♪♪ HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY ♪♪
♪♪ OHHH ♪♪
♪♪ OH ♪♪
♪♪ WON'T YOU COME SEE ABOUT ME?♪
♪♪ I'LL BE ALONE, DANCING,
YOU KNOW IT, BABY ♪♪
♪♪ TELL ME
YOUR TROUBLES AND DOUBTS ♪♪
♪♪ GIVING ME EVERYTHING
INSIDE AND OUT AND ♪♪
♪♪ LOVE'S STRANGE,
SO REAL IN THE DARK ♪♪
♪♪ THINK OF THE TENDER THINGS
THAT WE WERE WORKING ON ♪♪
♪♪ SLOW CHANGE
MAY PULL US APART ♪♪
♪♪ WHEN THE LIGHT GETS
INTO YOUR HEART, BABY ♪♪
♪♪ DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME ♪
♪♪ DON'T, DON'T, DON'T, DON'T ♪
♪♪ WILL YOU STAND ABOVE ME? ♪♪
♪♪ LOOK MY WAY, NEVER LOVE ME ♪
♪♪ RAIN KEEPS FALLING,
RAIN KEEPS FALLING ♪♪
♪♪ DOWN, DOWN, DOWN ♪♪
♪♪ WILL YOU RECOGNIZE ME? ♪♪
♪♪ CALL MY NAME OR WALK ON BY ♪
♪♪ RAIN KEEPS FALLING,
RAIN KEEPS FALLING ♪♪
♪♪ DOWN, DOWN, DOWN, DOWN ♪♪
♪♪ HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY ♪♪
♪♪ OHHH ♪♪
♪♪ OH ♪♪
♪♪ DON'T YOU TRY AND PRETEND ♪
♪♪ IT'S MY FEELING
WE'LL WIN IN THE END ♪♪
♪♪ I WON'T HARM YOU
OR TOUCH YOUR DEFENSES ♪♪
♪♪ VANITY AND SECURITY ♪♪
♪♪ DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME ♪
♪♪ I'LL BE ALONE, DANCING,
YOU KNOW IT, BABY ♪♪
♪♪ GOING TO TAKE YOU APART ♪♪
♪♪ I'LL PUT US BACK TOGETHER
AT HEART, BABY ♪♪
♪♪ DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT ME ♪
♪♪ DON'T, DON'T, DON'T, DON'T ♪
♪♪ AS YOU WALK ON BY ♪♪
♪♪ WILL YOU CALL MY NAME? ♪♪
♪♪ WHEN YOU WALK AWAY ♪♪
♪♪ OR WILL YOU WALK AWAY? ♪♪
♪♪ WILL YOU WALK ON BY? ♪♪
♪♪ COME ON, CALL MY NAME ♪♪
♪♪ WILL YOU CALL MY NAME? ♪♪
♪♪ I SAY LA LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA LA LA ♪♪
♪♪ WHEN YOU WALK ON BY ♪♪